http://www.ttcaps.com/privacy-policy

Contact UsUse the form on the right to contact us.You can edit the text in this area, and change where the contact form on the right submits to, by entering edit mode using the modes on the bottom right.
6310 Cane Run Rd
Louisville, KY, 40258
United States
1 (800) 626-2220
custserv@ttcaps.com
Custom embroidery on Visors, Caps, Hats, Apparel, and accessories.  Town Talk Headwear can help with all your staffing, team, charity, or tournament needs.  Ladies visors are handcrafted in Louisville, KY, USA.  All embroidery is done in Louisville, KY, USA.
Home
Custom Goods
About Wholesale
USA MADE VISORS
5 DAY RUSH
Custom Caps
Apparel
Embroidery
Monthly Specials
TALK!
INFO
ABOUT
blog
Contact
UPCOMING EVENTS
Sign In
My Account
Town Talk Headwear | ttcaps.com | #ttcaps
Info
Email
Search
PRIVACY POLICY
Privacy PolicyTown Talk Headwear values your trust and individual privacy. We recognize concerns regarding our collection, use, and disclosure of personal information that may be collected while using our Web site. Accordingly, we have implemented procedures as outlined in these Privacy Policy Statements:If you have any questions or concerns regarding the Town Talk Privacy Policy, please contact us.Town Talk Headwear never sells, leases, or otherwise reveals your email address or other personal information to any third party.Town Talk Headwear protects any personal information you choose to submit to us in secure, password- protected files that are not accessible to Web browsers.Town Talk Headwear may use cookies only to enhance the user’s on-site experience and to track overall on-site activity. However, cookies are never used to collect personal information on individual Web site visitors.
RETURN POLICY
GUARANTEE & DISCLAIMERS
Terms And Conditions
PRIVACY POLICY
